Hello friends, welcome to our YouTube channel Stock
Time. In this video, we
will discuss the
quarter 3 results of ICICI Prudential and ICICI Lombard.
We will also discuss the quarter 3 results
of Tata Metalik (TML).
Before starting the discussion,
if you haven't subscribed to our channel,
please do so and
click the bell icon. First, let's talk about
ICICI Lombard General
Insurance.
This is a press release issued by the company, in which
you can see that the company's GDP (Gross
Direct Premium Income) is ₹
54.93 billion, while in the previous year's
quarter 3, it was ₹
46.99 billion. The
company showed a growth of 16.9% in this. If we
talk about the next nine months, the
company's GDP in the last nine months has been ₹160.8 billion,
while in the previous year's nine
months it was
133.11%. In this, the company
saw a growth of more than 20%.  If we
talk about DBT i.e. Profit Before Tax,
it was 15.40 billion in the bank in quarter 3,
more than 4.65,
whereas in the 9 months of last year it
was 12.73 billion, the
company has shown a jump of 21% in this. If we talk about PET i.e.
Profit After Tax, it was
3.53 billion in quarter 3, whereas
in quarter 3 of last year it was
3.18 billion, there is a growth of 11% in this. If we
talk on the basis of 9 months, then the company's profit has been
12.5
billion, whereas in the quarter 3 months of last year the
company has given 9.5% growth. If we talk
about the company i.e. Benchmark on Average Equity, then
it
was 14.3% in quarter 3, whereas in quarter 3 of last year it was
14.6%. If we talk on the basis of 9 months, then
it has been 18.1%, whereas if we
talk about the 9 months of last year, it is
15.%
in quarter 3, whereas in the headquarter of last year
In 2022, it
was 104.5%. If we talk about the last 9 months, it
was 104.6%. Whereas in the last three quarters of last year, it was
11% continuously. If we talk about its performance in 2022,
it was 108.8%. Similarly, regarding Potential Life
Insurance, this is the
press release issued by the company. The
summary of standalone revenue and profit and loss is ₹
94.65 billion, whereas in quarter two it was ₹
95.82 billion. If we
talk about quarter three of last year, then it was ₹
90.74 billion. If we talk about its total income, then
it was ₹
173.54 billion, whereas in quarter two it was ₹
226.42 billion.
In quarter three of last year, it was ₹
98.38 billion. If we talk about profit before tax
i.e.
DBT, then
in quarter three it was ₹2.2.
If we talk about PET i.e. profit after tax, then
it was ₹2.2.  It
was ₹1.9 billion while in the previous year's quarter it was ₹
3.1 billion, that is, if the company shows a decline in it, then there has been an
increase in the company's net worth. In the 9 months of this year, the company's
net worth was ₹5.76 billion while in the 9 months of last year it was ₹5.69. According to the company, the company's
net premium earning has increased by 3.9% in 9 months, that is, this time the company's net
premium running was ₹
while in the three quarters of last year it was ₹
249.62 billion. If we talk about its total investment
income, the company has shown a decline in it. The
company says that this time there has been a
decline in it. In the three quarters of last year
it was ₹242.17
billion while in the three quarters of this year it was ₹
123.780. The total expense of the company has
increased by 15.4% in 9 months. The total expense of the company in the last 9 months has been ₹
46.98 billion while  In the three quarters of last year, it was ₹
40.72 billion. If we talk about its claim and
benefit payouts, then the
company has shown an increase of 4.2% in it.
As per 9 months, if the value of
new business of the company was ₹
13.8 billion, then the value of new business
margin has increased
this time as compared to last year. In the three quarters of last year, it was ₹
27.2 billion,
whereas in the three quarters of this year it was
32%. If we talk about new business received
premium, it was ₹
102.8 billion, whereas
in the three quarters of this year it was ₹
12.87 billion. The company has shown a growth of 10% in this.
Now let us talk
about TML i.e. Tata Metaliks.
In its quarterly results, the company has
reported a decline of 73% in its net profit. The company says
that its net profit in December was ₹
9.48 crore. Last year's
net profit was ₹
35.65 crore, however, its total income
definitely increased.
Its total income in the third quarter of last year has increased to Rs
693.2 crore. The
total expenditure of the company in the third quarter of last year was Rs
642.83 crore, whereas this year it has increased to Rs
780.8 crore.